She is the star of the play, and she is my girlfriend.
她是女主角，又是我的女朋友
I get to have sex with the star of the play!
我在跟女主角上床
-People can hear you. -I know!
別人都聽見了 我知道
She looks great,doesn't she?
她很漂亮吧？
That is one good-looking man.
那個男的可真帥
Is it just me,or can you actually see his abs through his overcoat?
是我眼花 還是他的腹肌真的露出來了？
So you been doing this long?
你做這行很久了嗎？
No. You're my first. Put the money on the table.
沒有，你是第一個 把錢放在桌上
That's nice.
好舒服
Dude!
不會吧
-ls that an expensive blouse? -lf you want it to be.
這件上衣很貴嗎？ 你說貴就貴
Here's your girlfriend's button.
你馬子的鈕扣
The One with Rachel's Crush
本集播出：「假戲真做？」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Do you still have your old blouses and dresses from high school?
你高中的衣服裙子還在嗎？
Yeah,I think I have some around here somewhere. Why?
應該還有幾件，怎樣？
Maternity clothes are so expensive.
孕婦裝都好貴
Rach,I made a pile of your stuff. If you could just...
瑞秋，那一堆是你的東西 看你要不要…
...throw your purses at it.
拿皮包扔它
Bloomingdale's eliminated my department.
布魯明戴爾裁了我的部門
Are you out of a job?
天哪，你失業了嗎？
No,but they stuck me in Personal Shopping,which is a huge step down.
沒有，但我被塞到專人採購部 當場矮了一大截
What is that?
專人採購部是什麼？
Where you walk around with rich people and tell them what to buy?
陪有錢人逛，幫他們挑衣服？
That sounds great!
聽起來好棒
We switched apartments. You can't eat our food. That gravy train has ended.
很抱歉，我們換房子了 你不能再吃我們的 好康的沒了
There's gravy?
有好康的？
If you have the big apartment,you have to deal with people coming over.
房子大就得應付人來人往
That fridge has to be stocked. That's your apartment now.
冰箱要塞滿東西 對面是你們的了
-What are you doing? -I think I left a doughnut up here.
你幹什麼？ 我留了個甜甜圈在這裡
How was Kathy's play?
凱西的戲怎樣？
Kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex with a real good-looking guy.
凱西半裸跟一個大帥哥演床戲
It's like somebody wrote down my worst nightmare...
這就像有人把我的惡夢寫成戲
...and then charged me $32 to see it.
還要我花32塊去看
That's a good idea for a business.
這個點子有賺頭
I'm totally screwed. They're gonna be hot and heavy on stage every night...
我毀了 他們會夜夜在台上打得火熱
...then they'll go to their cast parties, and he's gonna try to undermine me.
然後去參加劇組派對 他會設法中傷我
He'll be like,"Where's your boyfriend? What's his name? Chester?"
「你男朋友呢？」 「他叫什麼？錢斯特？」
She'll go,"It's Chandler." He'll go,"Whatever!"
她會說「是錢德」 他就說「隨便啦」
That is a good trick.
這招不錯
All right,look. What am I going to do?
我該怎麼辦？
They're actors. They're there to do a job.
他們是演員，那是工作
It doesn't mean they're gonna get together.
假戲不一定就會真做
Just because it happened with Susan Sarandon and Tim Robbins...
蘇珊莎蘭登和提姆羅賓斯的事
...doesn't mean it's gonna happen with them.
...不一定適用於他們
Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
亞歷鮑德溫和金貝辛格
Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman.
湯姆克魯斯和妮可基嫚 對
Mel Gibson and Clint Eastwood.
梅爾吉勃遜和克林伊斯威特
They're not a couple.
他們不是一對
I get the game now.
喔…我聽懂了
All these people were in movies together. It's much different with plays.
他們都是演電影 舞台劇差多了
You were in acting class together,and she slept with you.
你們只是一起上表演課 她就跟你上床了
Acting class is a lot more like a movie than a play.
表演課就像舞台劇裡的電影
When they were doing it on stage, was it really hot?
我問你 他們演床戲時很火辣嗎？
Oh,yeah.
是！
So you're fine.
那就沒問題了
The rule is when two actors are actually doing it off-stage...
如果兩個演員私底下在一起
...then all the sexual tension between them is gone.
他們之間的火花就會消失
As long as it's hot on stage, you got nothing to worry about.
只要台上很火熱 你就不必擔心
When the heat goes away, that's when you're in trouble.
熱度不見了才麻煩
Really?
真的？
You guys have been to every play I've been in. Have I ever had chemistry on stage?
你們看過我演的每出戲 我有擦出過火花嗎？
-No. -No!
沒有 對吧
Are you gonna go see the play with me tonight?
你晚上要陪我去看戲嗎？
I don't know how comfortable I am going to see how hot the sex is between them.
要我看你馬子跟別人有多火熱 我覺得很尷尬
-I know,but -No,I'm there.
我知道，但是… 我人在現場
-Want some pancakes? -You made pancakes?
摩妮卡，要煎餅嗎？ 你做煎餅？
Grab a plate.
對，拿個盤子
No,no. Stay right there.
別過來
Getting closer.
越來越近了
Don't worry...
放心...
...we also have cereals, muffins,waffles and...
...也有谷片、鬆糕、鬆餅
...jams,jellies and marmalades, which I'm sure are the same thing.
...和果醬、果肉醬和果皮醬 其實是同一種東西
Please eat,because Joey opened everything.
吃吧，喬伊什麼都拿來開
We're watching the game here Saturday night,if people wanna come over.
星期六要看球賽，歡迎加入
I was thinking about having people over.
我正想找你們到對面看球
Yeah? Who's playing?
是嗎？誰跟誰比？
The players.
球員跟球員
Somebody seems to be missing being the hostess.
有人在懷念當女主人喔
Please. It's a relief,is what it is,is what it is.
拜託！我不知道有多輕鬆
Pheebs,stick out your plate.
好，菲比，盤子準備
Monica,I'm quitting.
摩妮卡，我要辭職
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong,and she didn't even buy it.
我幫一個老女人塞上丁字褲 結果她也沒買
I'm quitting.
我要辭職
I'm talking to my boss right now.
我現在就要跟老闆說
Yes,I am. Yes,I am.
我要 我要我要我要…
Okay,bye. Call me when you get this message.
聽到留言請回電
Mr. Waltham? I really need to talk to you.
沃森先生？我有事找你
In a moment,please. I'm in the middle of a task.
等一下，我忙得不可開交
And you have a customer.
你有顧客上門
Hi.
你好
Hi,I'm Joshua.
我是約書亞
I'm Rachel Greene. What could I do for you,Joshua?
我是瑞秋葛林 有什麼需要，約書亞？
I need a whole new wardrobe. My wife Well,my ex-wife
我的衣服都要重買 我老婆…我的前妻…
I'm so sorry.
我真遺憾
Anyway,she burned all of my clothes.
她把我的衣服都燒了
I got away with this suit and what turned out to be a skirt.
我救回兩件，這件外套 和一條裙子
Well,at least that's a great suit.
這件外套很好看
It wasn't much fun dropping it off at the dry cleaners in the skirt.
穿裙子去乾洗店可不好玩
I need everything down to underwear. If you're willing,I'm all yours.
我連內衣褲都要，如果你願意 我整個人就交給你了
Okay.
好
You needed to speak to me?
瑞秋，你有事找我？
No,no,that wasn't me.
沒有，不是我
We should get started. Let me show you my underwear.
走吧，我帶你看我的內衣…
The selection of underwear that we carry.
我們的內衣專櫃
I'm sorry.
對不起
-It's this way. -This way? Sorry.
是這邊。 這邊？抱歉
I'm right. Right? There was no chemistry between them.
對吧？他們一點感覺也沒有
Before,they had heat. Now,there's no heat.
之前的熱度不見了
You know what this means. Joey told us what this means.
你知道個中含意，喬伊說過
Let's not jump to any conclusions. There was some sexual chemistry.
先別急著下定論 還是有一點點火花
Come on. It was like cousins having sex.
拜託，就像表兄妹在做愛
Here she comes. Don't say a word. Just be cool. Don't be,you know,you.
她來了，什麼都別說 冷靜，別跟平常一樣
Hey,you guys!
你們好
Thank you so much for coming again.
謝謝你們又來了
-Did you like it tonight? -Absolutely.
你喜歡嗎？ 那當然
Wasn't Nick funny when he couldn't get his match lit?
尼克點不著火柴時好好笑
It's a good play,isn't it?
這是一齣好戲吧？
I loved the play. You were great.
我很喜歡 你演得很棒
And Nick,ditto.
尼克也是
Clearly,you're having sex with him.
你顯然跟他有一腿
Okay....
好…
Clearly,I'm having sex with him?
我顯然跟他有一腿？
It was so obvious. There was no chemistry between you two.
太明顯了，你們之間毫無火花
You're accusing me of cheating on you, and you're insulting my performance?
讓我搞清楚，你先指責我不忠 又侮辱我的演技？
I can see how this could happen. You're up there every night naked,touching,kissing.
這也難怪 你們每晚都光著身體愛撫熱吻
Acting. Chandler,this is my job.
那是演戲，這是我的工作
I'm playing a part in a play. How can you not trust me?
我是在演出 你怎麼可以不信任我？
You can understand, given how we started.
我們就是這樣開始的
I can't believe you're throwing that in my face.
你居然拿這個來攻擊我
That is what happened. I don't even see you denying this.
事實如此，你剛才也沒否認
I'll tell you what,Chandler. You call me when you grow up.
夠了，等你成熟了再跟我聯絡
Don't expect that to happen any time soon!
那你可有得等了
I have the best job in the entire world!
我的工作最棒了
The most adorable guy came over, and I got to dress him up all day!
來了個最帥的帥哥 我整天都在打扮他
Rachel has a new doll!
瑞秋有新洋娃娃了
I wish he was a doll. I'd get a Rachel doll and bump them together...
真希望他是 我會把他跟瑞秋娃娃湊在一起
...and make kissing noises.
讓它們玩親親
He's got the most beautiful name. I never realized. Joshua.
他的名字最好聽了 我以前都不覺得，約書亞
Joshua.
約書…亞
Joshua. Josh.
約書亞，約書…
Hello?
Hi.
What do I smell?
什麼味道？
I don't know. It smells good.
不曉得，好香
Fresh cookies! Hot from the oven.
熱騰騰的餅乾，剛出爐的
Please,have some.
請用
I've been fiddling around here, making delicious treats for everyone.
我隨便弄了一些好吃的
The new Playboy.
新的「花花公子」
Just something I picked up.
我隨手買的
Cookies and porn? You're the best mom ever!
餅乾和黃色書刊？好棒的媽媽
What?
什麼啦？
It's just something Joshua said about V-necks,but you had to be there.
約書亞對V字領有些看法 現場聽才好玩
How does Jason look in a V-neck?
傑森穿V字領好看嗎？
-It's Joshua. -Whatever.
是約書亞  隨便啦
Wait. Wait. This isn't takeout!
等等，那不是要拿走的
-Hate to eat and run. -No,wait. Please,don't go!
先走了 別走
I've got porn for you too.
也有女生看的黃色雜誌
I don't need it.
我不需要
People are supposed to want to hang out here.
大家應該賴在這裡的
Why? What is the big deal?
有什麼關係？
I'm the hostess.
我是女主人
Not those guys. I'm always the hostess.
不是那些臭男生 我一直都是女主人
Even when I was little,the girls brought their dollies to my tea party.
連小的時候 別的女生都會來參加我的茶會
I served the best air.
我泡的空氣最好喝
Why'd you make a big thing out of everyone hanging out in the big apartment?
那你幹嘛叫大家去大的地方？
'Cause they took our apartment. I wanted to punish them.
我想罰他們搶走我們的公寓
I'm done now. They've suffered enough.
我罰完了，他們吃到苦頭了
If you wanted to punish them,you should have just made them hang out here.
要罰他們應該逼他們來這裡
That is true.
那倒是
This place is gonna be 10 times better than that place.
我一定會讓這裡比對面好十倍
Are we gonna trash their place?
我們要搗毀對面嗎？
There's steps!
台階
Slut!
賤人
You'll all be very happy to hear that Kathy is sleeping with that guy!
你們一定很樂於聽到 凱西在跟那個人上床
-What? -You were right?
什麼？ 你猜對了？
I confronted her, and she didn't deny it.
我當面問她，她沒有否認
I don't live here!
我不住這裡
Wait,are you sure?
錢德 你確定嗎？
I may be drunk, but I know what she said.
我是醉了，但我聽得懂她的話
Then I went over to Beefsteak Chewley's....
所以我跑去朱理牛排…
-Beefsteak Charlie's? -Yes!
查理牛排？ 對
You and l have always been like:
我們一向都很…
Man,I am so sorry.
真不敢相信 太糟糕了
The bartender taught me a trick,though.
酒保教了我一個小把戲
I don't remember it.
我忘了
-Do you need help with that? -I got it.
需要幫忙嗎？ 不用了
I just feel bad. I never vacuum.
真慚愧，我沒吸過地板
I was with Joshua for an hour today, and he has not asked me out.
我跟約書亞在一起1小時 他卻沒有約我
-Just so frustrating. -Why don't you ask him out?
真洩氣 那就你約他嘛
Totally. That's such a turn-on.
沒錯，感覺會很辣
Really? It doesn't seem desperate?
是嗎？不會很飢渴嗎？
That's the turn-on.
所以才辣
He just got a divorce. Right? He's probably really nervous around women.
他剛離婚 跟女人相處可能會緊張
Maybe you just need to make the first move.
你就先主動嘛
-I've never asked a guy out before. -You've never asked a guy out?
我沒約過男生 你沒約過男生？
No. Have you?
沒有，你有嗎？
Thousands of times!
幾千次
That doesn't make me sound too good,does it?
這不是什麼光榮的事對吧？
I don't even know how I would go about it.
我連怎麼開口都不會
What I do is,I look a woman up and down,and I say...
我會打量一個女人，然後說
..."Hey. How you doing?"
「你好嗎？」
Oh,please!
拜託
Hey. How you doing?
你好嗎？
You know what? I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna call him up and ask him out.
好，我現在就打給他 約他出來
I can do that,ask him out.
有什麼難的，約就約
"How you doing?"
你好嗎？
Hi,Joshua. It's Rachel Greene from Bloomingdale's.
約書亞 我是布魯明戴爾的瑞秋葛林
I was just wondering if you...?
對，我想問你…
If you...
問你…
...Ieft your wallet at the store today?
是不是掉了皮夾？
We found a wallet,and we
我們檢到一個皮夾…
The license? That is a good idea.
看駕照？真是好主意
Well,let's see. This license belongs to...
我看看，駕照是一位…
...belongs to a Mr. Pheebs.
菲比先生的
So sorry to bother you at home. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
抱歉打擾你，明天見，再見
-You've done that a thousand times? -I've never done that.
你做過幾千次？ 沒那麼矬
I just got so nervous that he'd say no.
我好怕他會拒絕
You gotta give him something he can't say no to,like...
你得讓他無法拒絕，像…
...Knicks tickets. Invite him to a Knicks game. You're guaranteed he'll say yes.
尼克隊的球票 找他去看尼克隊的比賽 他一定會答應
-Really? You think that'll work? -Absolutely. And if not,can I go?
你覺得有用？ 絕對的，否則我去行嗎？
What the heck is that?
什麼聲音？
Did she call?
她有打來嗎？
No. Sorry.
沒有，抱歉
Maybe I should call her.
也許我應該打給她
Forget her,man. You don't need her.
不要，別理她了，你不必受氣
He's right. What she did was unforgivable.
沒錯，她的行為很不可原諒
Well,yeah,but,you know, what if I was wrong?
對，但要是我弄錯了呢？
How might you be wrong?
你怎麼會弄錯？
What if she didn't actually sleep with the guy?
要是她沒跟那個人上床呢？
Tell me she told you this.
大哥，她有親口證實吧？
She didn't have to tell me. I saw the play. There was no heat.
她不必，我看了戲 他們毫無火花
-Back me up. -That's all you're basing this on?
羅斯，說句話 你就根據這個？
That's not backing me up!
這不是在幫我
Look,you said, "With the offstage and the heat"
你說私下如果有，台上就沒有
That was just a theory. There's a lot of theories that didn't pan out:
那只是個理論 很多理論都行不通
Lone gunman,communism,geometry.
孤槍俠、共產主義、幾何學
Oh,my God!
天哪
"Would you like to go to a basketball game with?"
你要不要去看籃球？
"It's funny,basketball, because I happen to have tickets"
籃球，真意思，我正好有票…
"Who likes the Knick?"
誰喜歡尼克隊啊？
What do you think?
你覺得如何？
Well,as a single woman, who is available...
以一個沒對象的單身女郎來說
...I think you look great.
我覺得你很帥
Oh,yeah. You look great.
沒錯，帥呆了
This looks great.
看起來真配
So you like it?
你喜歡嗎？
I do. I love it. In fact,I think I'll wear it home.
很喜歡 我決定直接穿回家
-Great. -Thank you so much for all your help.
太好了 謝謝你的幫忙
Well,I guess this is it.
那就這樣羅
Thanks.
謝了
Maybe I'll see you in the spring for the bathing suits.
春天再來找你買泳衣
You don't want to do that now?
你不現在買嗎？
That's okay.
不用了
I'll see you around sometime.
改天見
Basketball!
籃球
Sorry?
什麼？
I have two tickets to the Knicks game if you're interested...
我有兩張今晚尼克隊的球票
...just as a thank-you for this week.
好謝謝你這星期的惠顧
That would be great!
太好了
-Really? -That would be fantastic!
真的？ 對啊，太棒了
My nephew is crazy about the Knicks!
我外甥最迷尼克隊了
This is fantastic. Thank you so much,Rachel.
太棒了，謝謝你，瑞秋
Good morning.
早安
I just wanted to come over to say that I'm sorry.
我來說聲對不起
I acted like the biggest idiot in the world.
我真是最白癡的白癡
I can completely understand why you were so upset.
我明白你為何那麼生氣
I really wish you'd called me.
你怎麼不打來
Yeah,I know. I wish I had too.
我知道，我也很後悔
I think this is a good thing.
不過我覺得這是好事
We've had our first fight, and now we can move on.
我們吵了第一次架 可以進展下去了
I know for me,but
至少我確定…
Nick's pants?
尼克的褲子？ 對
I think our second fight is going to be a big one!
看來第二次有得吵了
-For next time,what do you say? -"l have an extra ticket."
下次要怎麼說？ 我多一張票
"An extra ticket." Not "two tickets."
是多一張票，不是兩張票
The first time you asked a guy out he turned you down?
你第一次約男生被拒絕了？
He didn't turn me down. He's at the game.
他沒有拒絕，他正在看球
I got the date. I'm just not on it.
我約到他了，只是我沒去
Okay,it's ready.
都弄好了
-Come on. -What's ready?
來吧 什麼弄好了？
Just come.
來就對了
Oh,my God!
天哪
This is beautiful!
好漂亮喔
Did you work for two days straight?
你整整忙了2天？
Pretty much.
差不多
What do you think of the floor?
這個地板好不好？
I don't know. Looks the same.
看起來一樣
You used to have carpet.
以前是鋪地毯
Oh,yeah.
對喔
I made snacks.
我做了點心
Please,just hang out.
你們隨便坐
I'm just gonna rest my eyes for just a little bit.
我要稍微瞇一下
Do you want us to come back later?
要我們待會再來嗎？
No,no,no. Stay. Just keep talking.
不，留下來，繼續聊天
I'm always the hostess.
我一直都是女主人
How'd it go?
怎麼樣？
-She wasn't sleeping with him. -Good!
她之前沒跟他上床 太好了
She is now.
現在有了
-What are you saying? -I'm saying that she is a devil woman.
什麼意思？ 意思是她很邪惡
You think you know a person,then they turn around and sleep with Nick.
才一轉身她就跑去跟尼克上床
Nick and his rock-hard pecs and his giant man-nipples.
尼克和他的大胸肌，大咪咪
I hate him. And I hate her.
我恨他，我也恨她
I don't hate her. I love her. This is all my fault.
我不恨她，我愛她 都是我的錯
How? How is it your fault?
怎麼會是你的錯？
I should have called.
因為我應該打給她的
If I had called her,she never would have gone out with Nick.
要是吵完我打給她 她就不會跟尼克約會
They wouldn't have ended up in bed. I threw her at his man-nipples!
他們就不會上床 我親手把她送給他
This is not your fault.
錯不在你
Your fight does not justify her sleeping with someone.
就算吵架她也不該跟別人上床
Well,if she thought they were on a break....
除非她以為他們分手了
Rachel,one of your customers seems to have left his billfold,a Joshua Burgen.
瑞秋，你的客人掉了皮夾 約書亞柏根
Really?
真的？
-Will you call him? -Yes,I will. Absolutely.
麻煩你通知他 好，沒問題
Hello,Rachel.
瑞秋
Hi,Joshua.
約書亞
-I left my wallet here on purpose. -Really?
我是故意留下皮夾的 真的？
Yes. I just wanted to see you again.
我想再見到你
I'm glad.
我好高興
Rachel,I'd like to say something to you.
瑞秋，我有話要對你說
Yes?
什麼話？
"How you doing?"
你好嗎？